[{"answer": "He knows how to fix things.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Why when Americans are about to vote now is he the guy to do the most important thing, turn round America's economy?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "I'm not sure where you got your facts but --", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Pull off a Chris Christie.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Why not say, my dad is going to crush him?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "If we keep spending $1 trillion a year more than we take in, and we keep saddling this country and the future generations with debt, none of those things matter.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "What comfort can you give young women that think that your father is going to come after them?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "This is --", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "How do you feel about this?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Not good at all.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Who's One Direction?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "We really don't.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Have you begun to think about what that could be like?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "So much enthusiasm.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Do you feel, though, that there's been a real change since that last debate, that there's been an irrational reaction in your father's favor because of the way he performed and indeed, the poor way that the president performed?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Very aggressive as teenagers.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "And what happens?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "He's busy being a doctor.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "And by the way, where is Ben?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "A bunch of malarkey?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "It's Irish.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "(INAUDIBLE) Mitt Romney across the stage?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Well -- well, I would push back on that.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "You would have been equally unimpressed, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well, let me say -- let me say this.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Why is this?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What on earth makes you think I fantasize about that?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I'm fine.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "It was a nice meeting.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "How did it go, the meeting with Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "I was, yes.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "I think you were raised Roman Catholic?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I'm not going to get into what each candidate believes or they don't believe.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Do you think he is a Christian?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "All wondering -- but they're all wondering if we vote for this guy, are we voting for somebody who essentially is a Christian?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "You ask him.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Don't you think it's a quite interesting debate, though?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "No, because I think as we get older, Piers, we do change our views.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Do you have any problem with that?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "The definition of marriage.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Gay marriage?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Listen, they can do whatever they want.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Why shouldn't gay people get married?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Can they get married or not?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Yes, sure.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Do you think it's a sin, homosexuality?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I'm glad my mother's not here.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Anything you want to share with me?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "He's doing well, thank you.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "How's your father?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Even beyond my worst fears.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Have your worst fears been realized?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I do agree with that.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "I doubt seriously whether that's, in fact, what has happened.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Do you see that in him?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Not at this late stage.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "Well, I think we have to allow for some light and shade and some perspective.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "What did you make of that, in particular the way the White House behaved in the aftermath?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "Is she just taking the heat away from Obama tomorrow night, do you think?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "I can certainly see where someone else would have a different view, but I think it is credible, particularly in the heat of an election campaign.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "In all your experience, is it credible that the White House, the president, the vice president, would have no knowledge of any requests from an embassy for extra security, particularly in a hot spot like Libya, where there's been so much attention from the White House in the last year?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Two points.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Or do you think it suited the agenda of the administration to not have this as a reminder that al Qaeda's alive and well and killing Americans?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "ATHER: Playing defense.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "Quick reaction to that, Dan?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "As skillfully as possible under the circumstances.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "Skillfully, do you think?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "TEWART: What happened really, I think, was that manufacturing went where labor was cheap and more plentiful, and more amenable to hard work.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "And how does the president that wins in three weeks time put it right?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "Well, I think it can come back.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "Is the genie out of the bottle, do you think?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "I think it's a big debate.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "Do you that think he's in that big a hole?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "MarthaStewart.com.", "docId": "121015pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "What's the website?", "qSentId": 763}]